Hello friends Mullah Mainu
Certified Interested Welcome back to my
YouTube channel today in this video
we will see some important things and along with this we will see
Nifty and I will start this video by saying first of all
if we look at it then here we have seen
overall market Lakshmi
and most of all midcap and
smallcap properties because if
you subscribe to the market then if you talk selectively then
here you can see that
before the findings are declared
we can see a father of side here
after this if we talk about Nifty's
Delhi Cantt question can consolidate now
because here Bollinger and
see this if you look at this Rotating Hormone then you have
a cup 201 first support in it there is a
tick here 1000 above the protein
which if it falls here then you can
see this leaf from around 30 then we
can see 2016 which can come here
because this is a problem in the market so
whatever you people here then let's
talk about it now  And because it is currently a great kara below itself
and its two,
then in the future also
you will get a little bit of love further cutting
Chittorgarh if it gives you 3200 if it is
about logging in you can
subscribe here if you get 33351 if you talk about
some important things like
tears bacterial technology Nestle
India this budget consumer care ICICI
Prudential pimples Tata Steel Products
acidity the
Indus Tower Delhi India at Alexi and
Mahindra & Mahindra Financial
Services some blue chips because at the
doctor's place and above that we have a
video channel so you must watch this video
you were going to move forward so this is the last almost
you will see a
little bit below the market
because this
question is going to be quite strong
so we should not
take any long entry in the market on English media and we just buy its
strategic planning and
in that case or only
invest in Scorpio stock, those who do this
that the market  If you can do a little and if
you talk about it, then here the
bill to be made in April is for profit in the market
and to support the market,
all the posts are by page,
so you
can also connect your entry here not by selective strokes,
but you cannot do it here all at once,
you just adopt my on lipstick and
add a little sugar here
and here if this can happen here by 2018, so
let's talk about
yourself,
tomorrow you can buy medicine when the market opens
and because the Indian Rupee comes to
74.50 against the dollar, then you will
not see any improvement in the overall market for a year, till then
you will get a little bit because we will see a little bit of it in the market, so
with this, if you
liked this video then like it and
subscribe to the channel,
you will get to see the details of your membership,
here we will show you the model portfolio
along with prepositional and multi-webpage,
select your details, if you want to know
about all those trade tests,
come and see the channel in the next video.